KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIME WORKER
Other people have been through
the same stuff.
They're similar.
Some people are just like me,
and I hope to save them with my rap.
Wow, super cool. It's amazing.
I mean, we don't often get
to go this deep with people.
Totally. It's great we got to learn
so much about each other.
I'm, like, so moved right now.
I run my own company
while I also work on my rap.
I don't want to lose sight of things
we take for granted.
Hey! Oh, God!
Oh, my gosh. He looks just like Jason.
- That's scary.
- He just appeared.
Hey, it's super-hot in here.
Don't be checking out her tattoos.
Hey, you perv.
- He wants to see my tattoos.
- You think so?
You want to join us? Oh--
After all that, for real?
He just walks away?
He's funny.
He was dying to see them.
- So funny. Right?
- Yeah.
CLASSROOM
BRING ON THE LOVE
WIN AT ALL COSTS!
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
TRUE SELVES LAID BARE
BRING ON LOVE
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
BAD BITCH
- She's back!
- Welcome back.
Okay, we wanna hear the whole story,
from the very beginning.
- It was amazing.
- Really?
Like how?
- Well--
- You're all smiles.
What is it?
You fell in love with him, didn't you?
You know, when he told me his whole story…
- Yeah?
- …it was like, wow.
It made me realize there's
a lot going on underneath for him.
- I see.
- Ah.
Like his past,
and his dreams for the future.
I was kind of surprised
by how mature he actually is.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
It's sensual in there.
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
RINRIN (20)
HOSTESS
- You two got closer?
- The sauna is insane.
- I'm jealous.
- It's seriously crazy.
- Wow.
- Nice.
- Kazuma was a mess.
- Really?
What was going on with him?
- He was pretty down about it. Right?
- Seemed deflated.
- He did?
- Yeah.
So, I was torn between Rune and Kazuma
the whole time I was in there.
Oh, really?
I felt bad for Kazuma,
but I was pretty sure he'd be fine.
Yeah, for sure.
I'm jealous he got to go.
I bet he'll come back refreshed.
- I'm so pissed off.
- I wish I'd gone.
Must be awesome.
- What's up, guys?
- Hey, man.
- He's refreshed.
- Look at his face.
- How was it?
- So refreshed.
It was great. So good.
- You lost weight.
- You smell good, seriously.
- I'm jealous.
- You smell so good.
- It was good?
- Incredible.
Did you talk a lot?
Yeah, we talked so much. Like,
about things I don't usually talk about.
- Personal stuff, about my mom and family.
- Gotcha.
Yeah, I felt like she drew it out of me.
- I see.
- Wow.
Yeah, she listened so intently
the whole time.
- Mmm.
- Are you two closer now?
- I think we are.
- That's good.
It was so good for us, for real.
Nice work.
The fact that you were chosen is nice.
That must've felt good.
- I was happy that she chose me.
- Yeah. Of course.
Clearly, Sara was thinking about you.
- Yeah.
- Mmm.
- I'm a bit frustrated, honestly, as a man.
We still have plenty of time.
- Did you go in?
- To the sauna? Three times, I think.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
- That's quite a lot.
- At least three times.
Three sauna trips? Why are you even here?
What are you doing?
But, seriously,
you went in there three times
- and still flunked?
- That's true.
- Hilarious.
- That's not good.
I'm frustrated.
I really wanted to go into the sauna.
I'm so frustrated about it, seriously.
Who would you have picked to join you?
Hmm…
It's a secret.
- I won't sleep now.
- I can't tell you.
Mmm.
- It's better that way.
- I see.
- That's true.
- Mm-hmm.
Can I see your tattoos?
What does it say?
Oh, that's my grandpa's kanji.
- "Sumi." His name was Sumito.
- Oh.
Why did you decide to get it tattooed?
- On my face?
- Yeah.
- He hasn't talked about it.
- That's true.
It's only on half.
- Okay, I'll tell you.
- Yeah, what is it? I'm curious.
- Don't tell anyone.
- Okay, I won't.
Okay, so,
I got it for my grandpa, because…
he was found dead…
Oh.
…and no one knows how it happened.
What? What do you mean?
They don't even know
if something criminal happened.
- Really?
- Yeah.
They just found his body.
And he had supported my dream
since I was a little kid,
but I eventually gave up on that dream,
for a new dream, to become a hairstylist.
And I never got the chance
to tell him I'd fulfilled that dream.
I see.
Since I was in kindergarten,
I played baseball and ran track.
And I told my dad that I only wanted
to do track and field, not baseball.
He told me, both he and my grandpa
had wanted to be baseball players.
And he wanted me to take over that dream
that never came true for them.
And I said, "Okay."
In junior high,
my team finished third in the country,
and I was in the top nine
for individual players.
I was the best center fielder in Japan.
Because of that, I was able to go
to high school on a scholarship.
But I could never
get into all the studying I needed to do.
Both was too much for me.
So I just gave up on everything
and quit.
Yeah.
And I had a falling out with my dad,
and my family ended up
falling apart after,
and we became estranged.
So, as a symbol of hope
that we would all reunite,
I decided to get my first tattoo.
And to honor my grandpa,
so that he'll wait for me
on the other side,
I got his name tattooed here.
These cherry blossoms
were my grandpa's favorite flower.
And bats are often associated
with the deceased.
And snakes,
I heard that they symbolize rebirth.
So, I'm hoping that my family
can go back to the way it was.
That's what the snake tattoo represents.
The rebirth of my family.
- An average person could never do that.
- To have them on his face…
- That's true.
- Right.
…that's some next-level determination.
My family went through a lot,
because of me.
I see. Oh, wow.
Once we started fighting, we split up.
I get it now. And this one?
My mom's name, in kanji.
It means "beautiful."
Oh, really?
- My face tattoos have the deepest meaning.
- Hmm.
It's my first time being around
a guy my age.
- It feels a little weird, you know?
- It does?
- Yeah.
- Bad weird?
- No, I don't mind.
- You don't?
- Yeah.
- That's good to hear.
If anything, I'm relieved
that we're the same age.
It makes me happy.
Actually, I just realized that
I'm open to someone my age now.
- Leave it to me.
- Yeah?
- I got you.
- Really?
I'm not like the other 22-year-olds.
I mean, I've just never interacted
with guys my age much.
- But now, I'm totally open to it.
- Mmm.
- Give me a shout if you need help, okay?
- Okay.
- Hit me up.
- Since I'm your age.
- Same age buddies.
- So much in common.
- This is a first for me, for sure.
- I mean, we should stick together now.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Sounds good.
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- Oh.
- He's so emotionally mature.
- Yeah.
- So, now we know.
- Mmm.
His face tattoos have definitely been
a topic of discussion on the show.
And it turns out they represent
his deep feelings for his family.
By the way, someone asked him,
"You went into the sauna three times
and still flunked?" But I don't know
if you ended up seeing that.
- Yeah, did we watch that?
- Was it three times?
I think that footage must have ultimately
been left out of the final edit.
Because I thought he never went in.
Apparently, his sauna scene
was incredibly boring.
Seriously?
- Like, unbelievably dry.
- But he's a hairstylist.
That's right. Maybe he got super nervous--
So you don't always get good footage
even on Badly in Love?
- That's right.
- So they cut his scenes?
We're not seeing the whole picture?
- Yes. There's so much more footage.
- Incredible.
- That's amazing.
- Because we can't use it all.
You know, I feel like Kazuma is becoming
more and more likeable.
Yeah, for real.
- On the blackboard, look what we wrote.
- What's that?
- "I will definitely win."
- Wait. What does it say? "Discipline me."
- No, it's "Definitely."
- Oh, "Definitely."
- But, does it say "whine"?
- It's not "whine."
"I will definitely whine!" Is that it?
- Why is he whining? What's wrong?
- Hold on.
It says "Definitely win,"
with an exclamation point.
There's no exclamation point though.
It's just a line.
- He forgot the dot.
- He's not exclaiming.
- Part of his charm.
- It says, "Whine!"
- It's not "Whine!"
- "I'm whining!"
Wait, hold on. I'm dying.
You're dying?
Don't die.
It is time for Ethics class.
Life begins when you stop
running away from your past.
Please reflect on
the mistakes that you've made
and discuss them amongst yourselves.
This time, Aya, you will speak first.
- No way, seriously?
- Nice, crush it.
- Why me?
- Let's go.
Okay, but, like, seriously?
Oh, man, for real?
Well, you know, from the time that
I was in second grade to sixth grade,
I was, like, abused.
And when I entered
junior high school, I had no outlet,
nowhere to put everything
that I was feeling.
And so,
I was pretty intense during that time.
Once I lost my temper,
I couldn't stop myself.
I'm still like that.
And so, like, with my younger brother,
honestly, I used to hit him and stuff.
I took my feelings out on other people,
on my mom, even.
To be honest…
me and my younger brother don't talk
to each other at all anymore.
My younger brother saw how I was,
and he said,
"I don't want anything to do with you.
I don't want people knowing
you're my sister.
So, just stay away from me."
And, you know, my room was
sort of a hangout spot for friends
when I was in junior high.
Like, my whole house was, actually.
We would drink, we would smoke,
and there were always guys coming over.
My younger brother
probably saw a lot of that.
So, he told me that
he didn't see me as his sister.
It was hard for me, of course,
but I thought, "Well, I can't blame him."
The police came to our house a lot,
because I would throw
these super violent tantrums.
So, he saw all of those things,
and naturally, my brother felt scared.
At least,
it seems like he was scared of me.
My whole family rides motorcycles.
Everyone.
But my younger brother refuses
to ride one, no matter what.
And, you know, I think it's because of me.
I think it's because he doesn't want
to be like his sister, in any way.
He told me to stay away,
to never speak to him.
I think I…
honestly, did something really terrible
to my younger brother.
When I started to go off the rails,
my younger sister was still very young.
I'd have some friends over,
friends I used to do bad things with.
I didn't think anything of it
at the time, though.
But when I asked her about it later,
she told me that
those guys scared her a lot.
But I was only thinking
about having fun at the time.
I didn't think about her at all.
But now I'm older,
and I've thought about it more.
And I feel bad for scaring her like that.
My sister's life is the total opposite.
She studied super hard.
- Mmm.
My younger sister's the same.
She studies a lot.
But my last name is unusual,
so the teachers at school
remember it easily.
- I had that too.
- Yeah.
My last name is Sagae. They'd say,
"That's Sagae's younger sister."
- Yeah.
- Mmm-hmm.
But, honestly,
she's not like me in any way.
She's very serious.
She studied hard
and got a university scholarship.
- Amazing.
- Wow.
Yeah. She did everything she could
to avoid causing trouble for our parents.
I was the oldest son,
but so irresponsible.
When I grew up and got a job, I thought
I should get my act together.
Maybe you could call him
and ask him to dinner.
- Right.
- And talk it out with him.
Even if it's embarrassing.
I mean, you're siblings,
so you should definitely talk.
- Express your gratitude to him directly.
- Right.
I haven't been able to say that
- to my sister. It's hard.
- Yeah, I haven't either.
It's kind of embarrassing--
You should be able to trust your family.
Yeah.
- It's a bond that can't be broken.
- Yeah.
And like, also,
I've been pregnant twice in my life.
Yeah.
The first time, I was 18.
And then, the second time I got pregnant,
I was 22 years old.
Yeah, but like…
they don't exist anymore, you know?
I don't know how else to say it.
But, back then, there was someone
I honestly wanted to be with forever.
And I got pregnant with his baby.
But at that time, like, when I was 18,
I wasn't taking life too seriously,
and I didn't have any money.
And, you know, the guy had his own issues.
But I still wanted to have the baby,
even if it meant I had to be a single mom.
But I decided to get an abortion.
And so, I had the surgery,
and when I finally woke up
from the anesthesia…
…I could really tell that
the baby wasn't in my belly.
How should I put it?
It was like that part of me
was completely empty.
That's how it felt.
I was like, "Oh, okay.
It's just gone now."
That was so hard for me. And, like,
I want to apologize to that baby.
Yeah, but it doesn't exist anymore,
so maybe there's that too.
Mmm.
You know, I actually had an abortion too.
I was… maybe 16 years old, I think?
I was living with my boyfriend
at the time, and I got pregnant.
At the time, I thought of myself
as very independent.
I went to the hospital, but I needed
my parents' permission to have the baby.
And they were totally against it.
So…
we fought a lot about
whether I should have it.
And I ended up having an abortion,
a major surgery.
There was this overwhelming sense
that it was gone, you know?
Waking up from anesthesia,
and feeling that it's gone,
I remembered that…
so vividly just now.
And then, that became part of my life,
it's part of my experience,
and who I am now.
Of course, it didn't end the way
I wanted it to, but,
I want to keep that experience
close to my heart.
That's what I was thinking,
listening to your story.
Mmm.
- Everyone's stories were so deep.
- Mmm.
- They hit me hard.
- Yeah.
This kind of deep conversation,
or a chance to talk about your past,
- doesn't happen very often, right?
- No, it doesn't.
But I realized that it's important
to have an opportunity to do that.
- Right.
- Yeah. But I feel so embarrassed about it.
Yeah.
Like, I don't even talk to my brother
or my parents about it.
I don't think you need
to be embarrassed at all.
I think…
your story resonated with everyone.
It reminded me that
I'll want to cherish my child
if I ever have one.
- We all felt it.
- Yeah.
Mmm.
I was like, "I want to have the baby."
But I got pregnant by a married man.
- I see.
- Yeah, he had a wife.
So…
I cried so hard. Then I got an abortion.
SHOW YOUR RESOLVE
I'm nervous.
- Hello?
- Hey there.
What's going on?
Nothing, really.
I just…
- Yeah?
- Is this her mom?
- Yes.
- Oh.
Like, when I was
still in junior high school…
Yeah?
…I was a bit rebellious, you know?
Yeah.
And, I mean, I never took
the chance to apologize to you
for all of that, so.
Oh, come on.
That's all in the past. Forget about it.
Sure, but, there's something else
I haven't told you.
- What?
- I couldn't, till now.
Uh…
I haven't told you
for about two years, but…
Yeah?
…I got pregnant with my second child.
- What?
- Yeah.
Mmm… Yeah, when I was 22.
But, of course,
I never told you about that, so…
I wanted to tell you now.
Ah.
Well…
don't let that happen again.
Mmm.
- I mean, it's a life.
- Mmm.
In the end, that child has no say in that.
Right.
Yeah.
- Life is extremely precious.
- Mmm.
You should think about that.
Mmm.
How long did you carry for?
Do you have an ultrasound photo?
I do. It's on my wall at home.
When I was pregnant
with you, Ayana, and your brother…
- Yeah?
- …for both of you…
- Mmm.
- I was told that
I might not be able
to carry you to term, but I did.
Right.
Firstly,
parents protect their kids.
Mmm.
No matter how far
they stray, or the trouble they have.
I would have risked my life
to protect you two.
That's honestly
all I could think at that time.
Mmm.
That's what raising kids is.
- Right.
- Yeah?
I mean, nothing can be done about it now.
But, you know,
I think I've said to you before, that…
I wish I hadn't been born to you
and that you weren't my mother.
Yeah.
Yeah. I wanted to apologize for that too.
I'm so sorry.
Well, you know,
whether it's something you regret
or something you feel good about,
the present only exists
because of the past.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
So, there's no need to apologize at all.
Mmm.
I'm still learning every day, as well.
Right.
I still make mistakes.
And there are times when I think,
"Oh, I'm glad I did that."
That's how everyone grows in life.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
You know, a parent would
never abandon their child.
Yeah.
But, like, thank you
for giving birth to me.
Sure.
- You've got a long life ahead.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Bye.
- She told the class her story.
- Oh, wow.
Ayacheru opened up
and shared her past with everyone.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Right?
Mmm.
I chose to get
- an abortion too, at one point.
- Oh.
It was during a time that my husband
was in and out of prison.
- I didn't think that I could do it.
- I see.
So ultimately,
I decided not to have the baby.
It's such a physical burden,
and mentally, of course.
Mm.
You know, men also bear
a burden in that situation,
and they may provide financial support,
and some men may provide
emotional support, as well.
Sure.
But it's the women
who physically experience it.
- Right.
- Mmm-hmm.
Even when they make the decision together,
a woman still ends up blaming herself.
That's why I think that
women need to try and be…
twice as careful as men,
in their relationships.
I think this Ethics class
is so good for them.
- Isn't it?
- More places should offer it.
Yeah.
You know, people usually try to look cool
when they're looking for partners.
But if you start by fully
opening yourself up, it helps so much.
- It takes courage. Because, you think…
- Absolutely.
…"How am I supposed to find
a romantic partner from here?
- From such a vulnerable place?"
- You're so right.
But you can. That's what…
this show is ultimately trying
to prove, right?
- Whoa. That's so wise.
- Thank you. You're so right.
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
Today, you will be helping out Ms. Higa,
who runs an orchard.
Please give it your all,
and help her as much as you can.
- Hello.
- Been a while.
Yes.
- Remember me?
- Welcome. I remember.
- You're back so soon.
- I flunked.
MS. HIGA
- That's fine. Keep trying.
- I'll keep trying.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- The ladies are always so beautiful.
- Oh, really?
Every time.
- It's the truth.
- Nice to meet you.
This building was already pretty old
when I decided to buy it,
about 45 years ago
- I see.
- I held church here for a while.
I was running a service.
But the number of people
has decreased so much
that now we go to another place
and worship together there instead.
Sometimes, there are people
who come and stay the night.
People who do gymnastics ask
to use it sometimes.
So, that's what happens here now.
As you set out to clean this place,
I'd be grateful if you cleaned
with the utmost care.
- Please be careful.
- Understood.
- Yes, thank you.
- Leave it to us.
- Let's start with the floor.
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- Ready.
And, go!
Wait, I can't.
Let's go.
Doing good!
Nice, nice, good work.
- Doing it right.
- Cleaning properly. Wonderful.
- There!
- That's insane.
I'm tired.
- It's pretty hard work.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Does the floor look clean?
- What'd you think?
- Oh, thank you so much!
- It's sparkling.
- Truly!
- Of course.
On Saturday,
about 20 people will stay here.
Okay.
They'll be children and teachers
from a nursery school.
- Oh, yeah?
- Thank you for coming.
- Your timing is perfect.
- Of course. Our pleasure.
Actually, this here
was made a while back
by the leader of the church.
THE CLOCK OF LIFE
This is such a great piece
of advice, for anyone.
- Let's all read it together, okay?
- Okay.
All right.
"The clock of life is wound but once."
"When the hands will come to a stop,
whether it's later,
- or much sooner in life…
- Louder, everyone.
…no one can know."
"The present is the only time you own."
"Live. Love.
And be sure to labor with all your heart."
"You must not count on tomorrow,
because tomorrow,
your clock of life
may have stopped ticking."
This is a very thought-provoking quote.
It's good to keep in mind.
You only live once, that's for sure.
- So live in the moment.
- Exactly!
- Do your best in the moment.
- Appreciate the present, right?
You all have a long life ahead of you,
so live for now,
and do your best in your life.
Don't waste your time, okay?
I will live in the moment
and focus on the present.
- Yes, right.
- Thanks so much.
Thank you for everything.
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
The clock of life.
Yeah, it was good. Live in the moment.
I feel like my mind is so clear now.
It felt so good.
The things you choose to do,
ultimately define you, after all.
Now, I want to know more about myself
about what I might be lacking,
and stuff like that.
- Does Ms. Higa live alone?
- Must be lonely.
Well, there are
some kids with disabilities living there.
Mmm.
Yeah, and there are children
without any relatives
who also stay there with her.
Okay.
Ms. Higa wanted us from part one
to spend time playing with the kids,
- if we had an opportunity to go back.
- Wonderful.
But that didn't happen.
Not for me, at least.
Oh, I see. I want to go back
and help clean again.
Same.
I want to give them something
they can keep.
- For sure.
- Like a gift.
- What should we bring?
- Or something else we could do.
It turned into
a wholesome brainstorming session.
- What can we do?
- I wonder what would make them happy.
Hmm.
If the kids are happy,
Ms. Higa will be happy.
- Right.
- True.
- I wonder if we can make a bench.
- Oh! Okay.
- That's a good idea.
- That's nice.
Yeah, we could make something together,
like a bench.
- And they can look at the view.
- Great idea!
- Awesome idea.
- The best!
- Sound good?
- Yeah! You're smart.
- Perfect.
- Awesome.
Stop, you're flattering me.
- Wasn't talking to you.
- Don't take credit.
I wasn't talking to you.
What's the longest relationship
you've been in?
- Five years.
- That's long! For real?
Maybe about six years.
- That's crazy.
- Five or six.
- I see.
- I thought I was gonna marry her.
- Wow, well, naturally.
- Yeah.
- That's when I was working construction.
- Why did you break up?
- Well, she was super pretty.
- Mmm.
So a lot of guys around me
were super jealous of me.
And they'd tell her they saw me out
with another girl, stuff like that.
It was too much.
- Oh, really?
- It happened a lot.
There were rumors with my ex too.
He cheated on me, like, six times,
and with the same girl.
- They'd started as friends with benefits.
- I see.
And I told him, "I'll kill you."
Kill him?
But I loved him too much,
so I forgave him.
So, yeah,
I haven't had a good relationship.
How many have you had?
- Ex-boyfriends?
- Exes, yeah.
- Just two.
- Two, huh? Same for me.
- You're lying. For real?
- No, I'm serious. Yeah.
Well, you were taken for five years.
- I started the bar after that.
- Oh, I see.
I've been running it for six years,
and I've been too busy.
A long time.
What's your blood type?
Worn-out type.
I'm just playing. It's B. I'm so sorry.
- My apologies.
- You're a B?
Oh, I see.
- And you? O?
- I can only get along with B.
- What? You're O.
- Nope.
- What is it then?
- People are usually put off.
- Are you A type?
- People are so put off by it.
- Come on, tell me.
- It's frigid.
No way!
- They're having fun.
- Looks fun.
- So, what's your blood type?
- AB.
- You're an AB?
- Yeah.
I see.
But all of my exes had
the same type, they were also B.
- It feels like we shouldn't be watching.
- Yes.
They're being so lovey-dovey.
They're having
such a lively, silly conversation.
- Can only happen if they like each other.
- So, they might be the miracle couple.
- Both born on this planet.
- Exactly!
- They are a good match.
- Might be a miracle.
- The girls.
- Hey there.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Morning.
Good morning. Good morning, everyone.
- Hey.
- You're dressed for summer?
How are you doing, lady?
I don't know how to respond to that.
Today, we have prepared
a date for you to enjoy.
Oh, here it comes.
The women will compete against each other,
and the winner will be able to invite
the man she's interested in.
- What kind of game?
- Beach flags?
Okay, everyone,
please change into your swimsuits
and head down to the beach.
- Wow, nice!
- Yeah.
Okinawa!
- Look, here they come.
- Whoa.
Nice.
Sexy.
Oh, my! Here they come.
Looking good.
Creepy.
- Why do you have a bat?
- Shut your trap.
You hear me?
Huh?
- It's starting.
- Yeah.
Today's competition is…
- a princess-carry race.
- Wow.
- No way!
- What the heck?
- What?
- What is that?
All of the women
will have to be princess-carried
- by the men in this race.
- What's that mean?
The first woman
to cross the finish line wins.
- Sounds fun.
- It's a fun game.
Ladies, please choose a man to carry you.
We're choosing one?
Please note,
the one you pick to go on a date with
does not have to be the same man
who princess-carried you
across the finish line.
This is the worst, seriously.
So, they could choose someone
they like, or someone they trust to win.
- I see.
- That's cruel.
It's cruel for sure, but I like it.
- This is exciting.
- This is about going for the win, right?
- I go first?
- Know who you'll pick?
"Going for the win."
Kazuma.
- Oh!
- Hey!
Uh-oh!
- Whoo!
- I'm jealous.
Kazuma. Now, Rinrin.
She's got such long legs.
So long.
Well…
I choose Ryopi.
- Hey.
- Gosh, such long legs!
I choose…
Rune.
- Okay.
- Whoa.
- Nice.
- Okay.
- So, who's it gonna be?
- Oh, shit.
Please.
- We're going for the win, so…
- Yeah?
…Kazuma.
- Whoa!
- Man.
- Double request!
- What happens now?
No way.
For real? Are you fighting over Kazuma?
- Look at you, Mr. Popular.
- He's so popular.
I had zero yesterday. That's how popular
I am right now.
He couldn't sleep at all.
- Kazuma, you choose.
- Wow, for real?
- Then, Sara.
- Yeah!
- Oh, wow.
- Thank you, please win this.
- I hope we win.
- She said, "Please win this."
Oh, Sharan, choose someone else.
Well…
- Tai-chan.
- I got this. Leave it to me.
You've got this.
This is your chance to show off.
- He's yours now.
- Damn it! Thank you.
- Don't go.
- Thanks, guys!
- Don't leave!
- Thank you. See ya.
Jump in.
- Wow, he went there.
- Oh, no!
Then what am I supposed to do?
All right, here we go!
We'll now start the princess-carry race.
- Speak louder!
- Let's go!
- Look at this. What is this?
- Let's go! Let's do this!
- We're going to win!
- You're carrying me. Let's go.
I'm going to win this to survive!
- I'm probably the strongest one here.
- Right?
- Based on strength alone.
- We'll win.
Everyone.
Let's do this!
In carrying position!
Can you do it?
- Yeah.
- Oh, nice.
Can my head be here?
- Yeah, sure.
- Oh, no, sorry!
Oh, no sweat.
- Ready?
- Wow!
Sexy!
I'll say, "Ready, go."
- Hurry up!
- Hurry! He's shaking.
- It's already fun.
- Yeah.
- Win, Tai-chan!
- Let's go, Tai-chan!
Ready…
- Go!
- Fire!
Your legs are too long!
- It's unfair!
- You're doing great! Go, go!
- Hey, that team fell down.
- They fell down.
I'm tired.
Oh, my God!
- Oh, Tai-chan is doing well!
- He's doing great!
- Tai-chan, go!
- Wow, amazing!
- Let's go, Tai-chan!
- Tai-chan is amazing.
- Your legs are way too long.
- Come on, man!
- Do your best!
- Tai-chan's gonna win.
Oh, my God.
I will win this race, so I can survive!
He's done!
I think I heard his spine snap.
Fight till the end! You can do it!
Let's go!
- Yeah!
- Oh, my God.
- Wow, Tai-chan is amazing.
- Here we are.
- First place!
- Amazing. Incredible!
Isn't this Tai-chan's
first victory in these games?
This is his first time winning a game.
- Second place!
- Oh, God.
I will never give up.
Strength of spirit! Endless grit!
Go, go, go! We did it!
Wow, thank you.
Shut up and enjoy the ride!
Nice one!
- Watch out, watch out!
- Oh, my gosh.
You idiot!
I'm terribly sorry.
- Tai-chan's incredible. Amazing.
- Tai-chan, impressive!
So cool.
- So awesome I got to see this side of him.
- He's so amazing!
This is what makes women
get the butterflies.
- You know?
- Yeah.
Girls like guys who can run fast.
- We do like that.
- All about the physical.
- That was awesome.
- It's crazy that everyone finished.
- Amazing.
- I didn't lose any stamina.
The winning female student
can now make her decision.
She will now go on a date
with a man of her choice.
There's only one person she can pick.
Rune.
- What?!
- No!
Yep, that's right.
He just carried her!
- What!
- Yes.
- Whoa.
- Are you serious?
That's crazy.
- Whoo.
- What?
It's all about Rune.
First, the sauna. Now, a date.
- So fast!
- All done, let's go.
- Seriously?
- Whoa.
- Let's go.
- Leaving?
- Later.
- Have fun.
Have a great time!
- Good luck!
- Hope it's fun!
- Let's go swim.
- Was it hard?
Let's have fun.
- Let's play, Tai-chan.
- It was hard.
- Wow. I feel like crying.
- Looked tiring.
But you worked so hard.
- Yeah, you did.
- For sure.
Is it his face? You think that's why?
It's his face.
This is the worst.
That's the first time I've seen someone
- sit like that in an interview.
- So cute.
It's like, "I'm the reason that you won."
Like, I just don't get it.
I went through all of that for you,
and you get to choose someone else.
I think, when Sharan
comes back from the date,
it'll be time for a serious talk.
It's hot.
- It's so hot, I'm dying.
- It is.
Oh.
- Thanks.
- This is a good photo.
- We're so photogenic right now.
- What is?
Is this your first time riding
behind a woman?
Don't say it like that.
This would put me off,
if it were me. "What?"
- I'd be like, "No."
- You'd be like, "No way."
- It's my first time.
- Is it? What, really?
Wow, I'm your first.
- Okay, let's go. Whoo!
- And we're off!
That's funny.
- It's so warm.
- So hot.
- This is great.
- Right?
- Are you excited?
- Oh, for sure.
- I'm a little scared, but excited.
- Here, let me adjust this.
- Okay, I'll go first.
- See ya.
It feels so good.
Hey, Rune, can you help me out?
Oh! Picturesque!
Whoa, this is incredible!
- It's beautiful.
- Gorgeous!
Ugh, they're on their date now.
- I'm jealous.
- I feel so bad for him.
Me too.
Let's give her hell when they get back.
Seriously.
It's kind of a big deal that Rune
has had two events in a row.
So, first of all,
why don't the guys come on to us more?
Why don't they? Yeah.
Maybe we're too aggressive,
so they don't feel like they need to.
- Maybe.
- Yeah.
- I guess that's true.
- That's what I think.
Seriously, these guys
don't have enough drive.
It's a perfect day for a date.
- It's the best.
- Her hair was blowing in the wind.
I mean, you guys won
and she chose another guy.
It's unbelievable.
- You're right.
- Seriously.
- I know.
- It's the girls' army.
- The girl army is here.
- The army has arrived.
Whoa.
Come over.
- All of us?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Jeez.
- They seem angry.
- What is it?
Are they angry?
I'm scared, I might pee my pants.
BRING ON LIFE
UNBEATABLE
So, us girls have something to say.
We want to know if you're serious.
And we mean all of you.
We're seriously wondering why you're here.
Especially you, Maru.
Are you actually here to find love?
That's scary.
I'm sorry, but I imagine, for girls,
guys like Maru seem cool and mysterious,
to put it nicely.
But, they're not like,
"Oh, I'm curious about him."
They're more like, "Take more initiative."
- Normally, I think that would be fine.
- Right?
- Mmm, mmm.
- But they want the guys to be men.
- Men with a capital "M".
- Capital "M."
- Right.
- Stop capitalizing it!
Come on.
- This is getting interesting.
- Oh, thank goodness.
It didn't take long to get
emotionally invested in Part 2.
- I am.
- For sure.
Part 1 is a distant memory for me.
So you can let go of Part 1?
It was fun while it lasted?
- Yes.
- I only remember Hentona.
Why? He only appeared twice.